Today we can announce
that we raised 3.7 million US dollars in
our first round
of funding for Nootonic.
This brings our company valuation to 20
million US
dollars,
and there's probably going to be quite a
bit of news and press surrounding
this. Just to let you know,
this doesn't mean we've sold the business.
It means we've brought on board some
exceptional talent and some people of
fantastic influence,
including Alan Barrett from Grenade.
Securing this funding means
that we can produce more stock,
more products, go into
more territories,
and finally take on the big challenge of
retail,
putting Nootonic into shops.
So we're hiring exceptional talent,
we're expanding
the team,
and we're looking to face those
complexities head-on.
I know it could seem from the onset
that when Chris and I started this project
about a year and a half ago, that we
were just two influencers looking to shill
a
product to make a bit more money.
It's two things.
First of all, neither Chris
or I have taken a penny out of the
business so far.
Even with the funding secured,
we're still not going to take any more.
Second of all, what we're building here
is a fully-fledged nootropic business
where
we are looking to try
and make the nation more productive.
There have never been more distractions
with social media,
alerts going off on your
phone,
juggling so many different tasks at the
same time.
And if you think about it this way, to us,
we feel productivity could be the next
fitness,
and rather than people needing a PB in the
gym or to run their fastest
5K,
some people just need to be able to commit
to lock in every day.
So a big thank you to everyone that's
bought Nootonic, tried Nootonic, enjoys
Nootonic,
and a big thank you to all the investors
that have bought in for our
first round.
And we're looking forward to growing this,
not just being one of the
most popular influencer drinks on
Instagram, but being one of the world's
biggest nootropic businesses worldwide.